<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="selectxpath.xsl" type="text/xsl" ?>
<!DOCTYPE annot SYSTEM "annot.dtd">

<!-- $Id: lincoln-thanksgiving.xml 41 2005-12-13 21:35:10Z orion $ -->

<annot>
  <head>
      <title>Lincoln's 1863 Thanksgiving Proclamation</title>
      <pubdate>bogus pubdate/version string</pubdate>
  <copyright>
      <year>1863</year>
      <holder>Abraham Lincoln (public domain)</holder>
  </copyright>
  <legalnotice id="tgiving-legalnotice">
      <address>
	<name>Abraham Lincoln</name>
	<street>1600 Pennsylvania Avenue NW</street>
	<city>Washington</city>,
	<state>DC</state>
	<postcode>20500</postcode>
	<country>USA</country>
      </address>
    </legalnotice>
    <svn revision="$LastChangedRevision: 41 $"/>
  </head>

<body>
<section id="tgiving" name="Lincoln's 1863 Thanksgiving Proclamation">

<p id="tgiving.p2">
 <sent id="tgiving.p2.s1">The year that is drawing towards its close, has been filled with the
blessings of fruitful fields and healthful skies.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p2.s2">To these bounties,
which are so constantly enjoyed that we are prone to forget the source
from which they come, others have been added, which are of so
extraordinary a nature, that they cannot fail to penetrate and soften
even the heart which is habitually insensible to the ever watchful
providence of Almighty God.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p2.s3">In the midst of a civil war of unequalled
magnitude and severity, which has sometimes seemed to foreign States
to invite and to provoke their aggression, peace has been preserved
with all nations, order has been maintained, the laws have been
respected and obeyed, and harmony has prevailed everywhere except in
the theatre of military conflict; while that theatre has been greatly
contracted by the advancing armies and navies of the Union.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p2.s4">Needful
diversions of wealth and of strength from the fields of peaceful
industry to the national defence, have not arrested the plough, the
shuttle, or the ship; the axe had enlarged the borders of our
settlements, and the mines, as well of iron and coal as of the
precious metals, have yielded even more abundantly than
heretofore.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p2.s5">Population has steadily increased, notwithstanding the
waste that has been made in the camp, the siege and the battle-field;
and the country, rejoicing in the consciousness of augmented strength
and vigor, is permitted to expect continuance of years with large
increase of freedom.</sent>
</p>

<p id="tgiving.p3">
 <sent id="tgiving.p3.s1">No human counsel hath devised nor hath any mortal hand worked out
these great things.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p3.s2">They are the gracious gifts of the Most High God,
who, while dealing with us in anger for our sins, hath nevertheless
remembered mercy.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p3.s3">It has seemed to me fit and proper that they should
be solemnly, reverently and gratefully acknowledged as with one heart
and voice by the whole American People.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p3.s4">I do therefore invite my
fellow citizens in every part of the United States, and also those who
are at sea and those who are sojourning in foreign lands, to set apart
and observe the last Thursday of November next, as a day of
Thanksgiving and Praise to our beneficent Father who dwelleth in the
Heavens.</sent>
 <sent id="tgiving.p3.s5">And I recommend to them that while offering up the
ascriptions justly due to Him for such singular deliverances and
blessings, they do also, with humble penitence for our national
perverseness and disobedience, commend to his tender care all those
who have become widows, orphans, mourners or sufferers in the
lamentable civil strife in which we are unavoidably engaged, and
fervently implore the interposition of the Almighty Hand to heal the
wounds of the nation and to restore it as soon as may be consistent
with the Divine purposes to the full enjoyment of peace, harmony,
tranquillity and Union.</sent>
</p>

<p id="tgiving.p4">
 <sent id="tgiving.p4.s1">Abraham Lincoln</sent>
</p>
</section>
</body>
</annot>