<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="selectxpath.xsl" type="text/xsl" ?>
<!DOCTYPE gpl SYSTEM "http://gplv3.fsf.org/comments/gpl3.dtd">
<!-- $Id$ -->
<gpl>
  <head>
    <title>GNU Free Documentation License</title>
    <pubdate>Discussion Draft 1 of Version 2, September 2006</pubdate>
<status>THIS IS A DRAFT, NOT A PUBLISHED VERSION OF THE GNU SIMPLER FREE DOCUMENTATION LICENSE.</status> 
    <copyright>
      <year>2000, 2002, 2006</year>
      <holder>Free Software Foundation, Inc.</holder>
    </copyright>
    <legalnotice>
      <address>
        <name>Free Software Foundation, Inc.</name>
        <street>51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor</street>,
        <city>Boston</city>,
        <state>MA</state>
        <postcode>02110-1301</postcode>
        <country>USA</country>
      </address>
      <p>Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.</p>
    </legalnotice>
    <releaseinfo>Mon 25 September 2006</releaseinfo>
    </head>

  <body>
    <title>GNU Free Documentation License</title>

<section id="gfdl.whatdoes" name="0. WHAT THIS LICENSE DOES">
<title>0. WHAT THIS LICENSE DOES</title>
<p id="gfdl.whatdoes.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p0.s1">The purpose of this License is to make a work of authorship free.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p0.s2">This means giving all users the four essential freedoms:</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s1">0.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s2">The freedom to read, view, or use the work.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s3">1.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s4">The freedom to change the work, with access to formats
     which make that convenient to do.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s5">2.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s6">The freedom to make and redistribute copies of the work.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s7">3.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p1.s8">The freedom to distribute modified versions.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.whatdoes.p2">
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p2.s1">Secondarily, this License assures the author and publisher the credit
for their work, while sparing them any appearance of being responsible
for modifications made by others.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.whatdoes.p3">
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p3.s1">This License is a kind of "copyleft", which means that derivative
works of the document must themselves be free in the same sense.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p3.s2">It
complements the GNU General Public License, which is a copyleft
license designed for free software.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.whatdoes.p4">
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p4.s1">This License is not limited to "documentation", or even to works that
are textual; it can be used for any work of authorship meant for human
appreciation, rather than machine execution.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p4.s2">We recommend this
License principally for works whose purpose is instruction or
reference, but it can be used for any work regardless of the subject
matter, even for art and fiction.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.whatdoes.p4.s3">The only kind of work for which
this should not be used is software.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.applicdef" name="1. APPLICABILITY AND DEFINITIONS">
<title>1. APPLICABILITY AND DEFINITIONS</title>
<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p0.s1">In this License, each licensee is addressed as "you," while "the
Work" refers to any work, in any medium, that contains a notice placed
by the copyright holder saying it can be distributed under the terms
of this License.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p0.s2">It may physically consist of multiple volumes.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p0.s3">A
"modified" work includes versions that have been translated,
transformed, or adapted, or to which material has been added.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p0.s4">A work
"based on" another work means any modified version for which
permission is necessary under applicable copyright law.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p1.s1">To "propagate" a work means doing anything with it that requires
permission under applicable copyright law, except making modifications
that you do not share.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p1.s2">Propagation includes copying, distribution
(with or without modification), making available or communicating to
the public,publicly displaying or performing the work and in some
countries other activities as well.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p1.s3">To "convey" a work means any kind
of propagation that enables other parties to make or receive copies,
excluding sublicensing.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p2">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p2.s1">An "Ancillary Section" is a named section preceding or following the
main body of the Work that deals exclusively with the relationship of
the publishers or authors of the Work to the Work's overall subject
(or to related matters) and contains nothing that could fall directly
within that overall subject.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p2.s2">(Thus, if the Work is in part a textbook
of mathematics, an Ancillary Section may not explain any mathematics.)</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p2.s3">The relationship could be a matter of historical connection with the
subject or with related matters, or of legal, commercial,
philosophical, ethical or political position regarding them.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p3">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p3.s1">The "Invariant Sections" are certain Ancillary Sections whose titles
are designated, as being those of Invariant Sections, in the notice
that says that the Work is released under this License.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p3.s2">If a
section does not fit the above definition of Ancillary then it is not
allowed to be designated as Invariant.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p3.s3">The Work may contain zero
Invariant Sections.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p3.s4">If the Work does not identify any Invariant
Sections then there are none.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p4">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p4.s1">The "Cover Texts" are certain short passages of text that are listed,
as Front-Cover Texts or Back-Cover Texts, in the notice that says that
the Work is released under this License.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p4.s2">A Front-Cover Text may
be at most 5 words, and a Back-Cover Text may be at most 25 words.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p5">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p5.s1">A "Transparent" copy of the Work means a machine-readable copy,
represented in a format whose specification is available to the
general public, that is suitable for revision straightforwardly by
generic editors appropriate to the medium (text, sound, video, etc.),
and that is suitable (perhaps through programmed format conversion) for
input to a wide variety of programs for processing that medium.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p5.s2">Material stored in an otherwise Transparent file format in a way that
thwarts or discourages subsequent substantial modification by others
is not Transparent.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p5.s3">A copy that is not "Transparent" is called
"Opaque".</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p6">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p6.s1">Examples of suitable formats for Transparent copies of textual works
include plain ASCII without markup, Texinfo input format, LaTeX input
format, SGML or XML using a publicly available DTD or schema,
OpenDocument format, and standard-conforming simple HTML, PostScript
or PDF designed for human modification.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p6.s2">Examples of transparent image
formats include PNG, XCF and JPG.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p6.s3">Examples of transparent video
formats include MPEG2 and Ogg Theora.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p6.s4">Opaque formats include
proprietary formats that can be read and edited only by proprietary
word processors, SGML or XML for which the DTD, schema and/or
processing tools are not generally available, and the
machine-generated HTML, PostScript or PDF produced by some word
processors for output purposes only.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p7">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p7.s1">The "Title Page" means the portion of the work where information such
as title, authors, date of publication, and copyright notice would
normally appear.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p8">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p8.s1">A section "Entitled XYZ" means a named section of the Work whose
title either is precisely XYZ or contains XYZ in parentheses following
text that translates XYZ in another language.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p8.s2">(Here XYZ stands for a
specific section name mentioned below, such as "Acknowledgements",
"Dedications", "Endorsements", or "History".)</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p8.s3">To "Preserve the Title"
of such a section when you modify the Work means that it remains a
section "Entitled XYZ" according to this definition.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.applicdef.p9">
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p9.s1">The Work may include Warranty Disclaimers next to the notice which
states that this License applies to the Work.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.applicdef.p9.s2">These Warranty
Disclaimers are considered to be included by reference in this
License, but only as regards disclaiming warranties: any other
implication that these Warranty Disclaimers may have is void and has
no effect on the meaning of this License.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.basicpermissions" name="1a. BASIC PERMISSIONS">
<title>1a. BASIC PERMISSIONS</title>
<p id="gfdl.basicpermissions.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.basicpermissions.p0.s1">You have a world-wide, royalty-free license, for the duration of the
copyright on the Work, to use the Work under the conditions stated
herein.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.basicpermissions.p0.s2">You accept the license if you propagate the Work.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.verbatimcopying" name="2. VERBATIM COPYING">
<title>2. VERBATIM COPYING</title>
<p id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p0.s1">You may propagate the Work unmodified in any medium, either commercially or
noncommercially, provided that this License, the copyright notices,
and the license notice saying this License applies to the Work are
reproduced in all copies, and that you add no other conditions
whatsoever to those of this License.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p1.s1">You need not include a copy of this License in the Work if you have
registered the work's license with a national agency that maintains a
network server through which the general public can find out its
license.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p2">
 <sent id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p2.s1">You may not apply technical measures to obstruct or control the use or
further copying of any copies you make or distribute, by those to whom
they may be distributed.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p2.s2">However, you may charge a fee in exchange
for copies.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p2.s3">You may transmit copies with methods that give you legal
rights to control further use, copying or transmission, only on
condition that you waive the use of those legal rights to impose any
conditions aside from those of this License.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p3">
 <sent id="gfdl.verbatimcopying.p3.s1">You may publically perform the Work provided you make a transparent
copy available as described in section 3 as though you had propagated
opaque copies to the audience.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.copyinginquantity" name="3. COPYING IN QUANTITY">
<title>3. COPYING IN QUANTITY</title>
<p id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p0.s1">If you publish printed copies (or copies in media that commonly have
printed covers) of the Work, numbering more than 100, and the Work's
license notice requires Cover Texts, you must enclose the copies in
covers that carry, clearly and legibly, all these Cover Texts:
Front-Cover Texts on the front cover, and Back-Cover Texts on the back
cover.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p0.s2">Both covers must also clearly and legibly identify you as the
publisher of these copies.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p0.s3">The front cover must clearly and
unambiguously present the full title.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p0.s4">Copying with changes limited to
the covers, under these conditions, can be treated as verbatim copying
in other respects.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p1.s1">If the required texts for either cover are too voluminous to fit
legibly, you should put the first ones listed (as many as fit
reasonably) on the actual cover, and continue the rest onto adjacent
pages.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p2">
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p2.s1">If you convey Opaque copies of the Work numbering more than 100, you
must also convey a corresponding machine-readable Transparent version.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p2.s2">The Transparent version need not have identical formatting as long as
its contents are the same and are clearly visible, and non-textual
contents have equal or superior resolution and quality.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p2.s3">When you
convey the Opaque copies by offering access to copy from a designated
place, you must offer equivalent access to copy the Transparent
version from the same place.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p2.s4">Otherwise, you must convey a
machine-readable Transparent copy along with each Opaque copy, or
state in or with each Opaque copy a computer-network location from
which the general network-using public has anonymous gratis access to
download, using public-standard network protocols, a corresponding
Transparent copy of the Work.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p2.s5">Under the latter option, you must take
reasonably prudent steps, when you begin conveying Opaque copies in
quantity, to ensure that this Transparent copy will remain thus
accessible at the stated location until at least one year after the
last time you convey an Opaque copy (directly or through your agents
or retailers) of that edition to the public.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p3">
 <sent id="gfdl.copyinginquantity.p3.s1">It is requested, but not required, that you contact the authors of the
Work well before conveying any large number of copies, to give
them a chance to provide you with an updated version of the Work.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.modifications" name="4. MODIFICATIONS">
<title>4. MODIFICATIONS</title>
<p id="gfdl.modifications.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p0.s1">You may convey a Modified Version of the Work under the conditions of
sections 2 and 3 above, provided that you release the Modified Version
under precisely this License, with the Modified Version filling the
role of the Work, thus licensing distribution and modification of the
Modified Version to whoever possesses a copy of it.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p0.s2">In addition, you
must do these things in the Modified Version:</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.modifications.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s1">A. Use in the Title Page (and on the covers, if any) a title distinct
   from that of the Work, and from those of previous versions as
   listed in the History section.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s3">B. List as authors (on the Title Page, if any), one or more persons or entities
   responsible for authorship of the modifications in the Modified Version.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s4">C. Credit (on the Title Page, if any) at least five of the principal authors of
   the Work (all of them, if it has fewer than five) if the material
   derived from the Work is more than 1/4 of the total.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s5">D. Prominently state the name of the publisher of the Modified Version.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s6">E. Preserve all the copyright notices of the Work.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s7">F. Add an appropriate copyright notice for your modifications
   adjacent to the other copyright notices.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s8">G. Include, immediately after the copyright notices, a license notice
   giving the public permission to use the Modified Version under the
   terms of this License, in the form shown in the Addendum below.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s9">H. Preserve in that license notice the full lists of Invariant Sections
   and required Cover Texts given in the Work's license notice.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s10">I. Include an unaltered copy of this License.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s11">J. Preserve the section Entitled "History", Preserve its Title, and add
   to it an item stating at least the title, year, new authors, and
   publisher of the Modified Version.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s12">If
   there is no section Entitled "History" in the Work, create one
   stating the title, year, authors, and publisher of the Work,
   then add an item describing the Modified
   Version as stated in the previous sentence.</sent><br>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s13">K. Preserve the network location, if any, given in the Work for
   public access to a Transparent copy of the Work, and likewise
   the network locations given in the Work for previous versions
   it was based on.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s14">These may be placed in the "History" section.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s15">You may omit a network location for a work that was published at
   least four years before the Work itself.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s16">L. For any section Entitled "Acknowledgements" or "Dedications",
   Preserve the Title of the section, and preserve in the section all
   the substance and tone of each of the contributor acknowledgements
   and/or dedications given therein.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s17">Acknowledgments and Dedications
   can be deleted when a Modified Version deletes all material to
   which the Acknowledgments and Dedications could reasonably have
   applied.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s18">M. Preserve all the Invariant Sections of the Work, unaltered in
   their text and in their titles.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s19">Section numbers
   or the equivalent are not considered part of the section titles.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s20">N. Delete any section Entitled "Endorsements".</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s21">Such a section
   may not be included in the Modified Version.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s22">O. Do not retitle any existing section to be Entitled "Endorsements"
   or to conflict in title with any Invariant Section.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p1.s23">P. Preserve any Warranty Disclaimers.<br/></sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.modifications.p2">
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p2.s1">Authors and publishers of previous versions can release you from above
requirements to cite or refer to them or their versions.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.modifications.p3">
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p3.s1">If the Modified Version includes Ancillary Sections that contain no
material copied from the Work, you may at your option designate some
or all of these sections as invariant.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p3.s2">To do this, add their titles
to the list of Invariant Sections in the Modified Version's license
notice.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p3.s3">These titles must be distinct from any other section titles.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.modifications.p4">
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p4.s1">You may add a section Entitled "Endorsements", provided it contains
nothing but endorsements of your Modified Version by various
parties--for example, statements of peer review or that the text has
been approved by an organization as the authoritative definition of a
standard.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.modifications.p5">
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p5.s1">You may add a passage of up to five words as a Front-Cover Text, and a
passage of up to 25 words as a Back-Cover Text, to the end of the list
of Cover Texts in the Modified Version.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p5.s2">Only one passage of
Front-Cover Text and one of Back-Cover Text may be added by (or
through arrangements made by) any one entity.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p5.s3">If the Work already
includes a cover text for the same cover, previously added by you or
by arrangement made by the same entity you are acting on behalf of,
you may not add another; but you may replace the old one, on explicit
permission from the previous publisher that added the old one.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.modifications.p6">
 <sent id="gfdl.modifications.p6.s1">The author(s) and publisher(s) of the Work do not by this License
give permission to use their names for publicity for or to assert or
imply endorsement of any Modified Version.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.combinations" name="5. COMBINATIONS">
<title>5. COMBINATIONS</title>
<p id="gfdl.combinations.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.combinations.p0.s1">You may combine the Work with other works released under this License,
under the terms defined in section 4 above for modified versions,
provided that you include in the combination all of the Invariant
Sections of all of the original works, unmodified, and list them all
as Invariant Sections of your combined work in its license notice, and
that you preserve all their Warranty Disclaimers.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.combinations.p0.s2">Clause 4C applies
to all the principal authors of all the combined works, taken
together.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.combinations.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.combinations.p1.s1">The combined work need only contain one copy of this License, and
multiple identical Invariant Sections may be replaced with a single
copy.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.combinations.p1.s2">If there are multiple Invariant Sections with the same name but
different contents, make the title of each such section unique by
adding a unique number at the end.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.combinations.p1.s3">Make the same adjustment to the
section titles in the list of Invariant Sections in the license notice
of the combined work.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.combinations.p2">
 <sent id="gfdl.combinations.p2.s1">In the combination, you must preserve all warranty disclaimers,
combine any sections Entitled "History" in the various original
works, forming one section Entitled "History"; likewise combine
any sections Entitled "Acknowledgements", and any sections Entitled
"Dedications".</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.combinations.p2.s2">You must delete all sections Entitled "Endorsements".</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.collections" name="6. COLLECTIONS">
<title>6. COLLECTIONS</title>
<p id="gfdl.collections.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.collections.p0.s1">You may make a collection consisting of the Work and other works
released under this License, and replace the individual copies of this
License in the various works with a single copy that is included in
the collection, provided that you follow the rules of this License for
verbatim copying of each of the works in all other respects.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.collections.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.collections.p1.s1">You may extract one of the collected works from such a collection, and
distribute it individually under this License, provided you insert a
copy of this License into the extracted work, and follow this License
in all other respects regarding verbatim copying of that work.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.excerpts" name="6a. EXCERPTS">
<title>6a. EXCERPTS</title>
<p id="gfdl.excerpts.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.excerpts.p0.s1">You may publish a work, a Modified Version, or a collection, of up
to 20,000 characters of text (excluding formatting mark-up) in
electronic form, or up to 12 normal printed pages, or up to a minute
of audio or video, as an Excerpt.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.excerpts.p0.s2">An Excerpt follows the applicable
rules of this license, except that the following required
materials--the copy of this license, title page materials, historical
copyright notices, warranty disclaimers, and any required
sections--may be replaced by one or more publicly accessible URLs
referring to the same materials.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.aggregation" name="7. AGGREGATION WITH INDEPENDENT WORKS">
<title>7. AGGREGATION WITH INDEPENDENT WORKS</title>
<p id="gfdl.aggregation.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.aggregation.p0.s1">A compilation of the Work or its derivatives with other separate and
independent works, in or on a volume of a storage or distribution
medium, is called an "aggregate" if the compilation and the copyright
resulting from the compilation are not used to limit the legal rights
of the compilation's users beyond what the individual works permit.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.aggregation.p0.s2">Including the Work in an aggregate does not cause this License to
apply to the other works in the aggregate which are not themselves
derivative works of the Work.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.aggregation.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.aggregation.p1.s1">If the Cover Text requirement of section 3 is applicable to these
copies of the Work, then if the Work is less than one half of
the entire aggregate, the Work's Cover Texts may be placed on
covers that bracket the Work within the aggregate, or the
electronic equivalent of covers if the Work is in electronic form.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.aggregation.p1.s2">Otherwise they must appear on printed covers that bracket the whole
aggregate.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.translation" name="8. TRANSLATION">
<title>8. TRANSLATION</title>
<p id="gfdl.translation.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.translation.p0.s1">Translation is considered a kind of modification, so you may
distribute translations of the Work under the terms of section 4.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.translation.p0.s2">Replacing Invariant Sections with translations requires special
permission from their copyright holders, but you may include
translations of some or all Invariant Sections in addition to the
original versions of these Invariant Sections.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.translation.p0.s3">You may include a
translation of this License, and all the license notices in the
Work, and any Warrany Disclaimers, provided that you also include
the original English version of this License and the original versions
of those notices and disclaimers.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.translation.p0.s4">In case of a disagreement between
the translation and the original version of this License or a notice
or disclaimer, the original version will prevail.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.translation.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.translation.p1.s1">If a section in the Work is Entitled "Acknowledgements",
"Dedications", or "History", the requirement (section 4) to Preserve
its Title (section 1) will typically require changing the actual
title.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.sfdlrelicensing" name="8a. SFDL RELICENSING">
<title>8a. SFDL RELICENSING</title>
<p id="gfdl.sfdlrelicensing.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.sfdlrelicensing.p0.s1">If the Work has no Cover Texts and no Invariant Sections then you may
relicense the Work under the GNU Simple Free Documentation License.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gfdl.wikirelicensing" name="[8b. WIKI RELICENSING">
<title>[8b. WIKI RELICENSING</title>

<p id="gfdl.wikirelicensing.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.wikirelicensing.p0.s1">If the Work was previously published, with no Cover Texts, no
Invariant Sections, and no Acknowledgements or Dedications or
Endorsements section, in a system for massive public collaboration
under version 1.2 of this License, and if all the material in the Work
was either initially developed in that collaboration system or had
been imported into it before 1 June 2006, then you may relicense the
Work under the GNU Wiki License.]</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.termination" name="9. TERMINATION">
<title>9. TERMINATION</title>
<p id="gfdl.termination.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.termination.p0.s1">You may not propagate or modify the Work except as
expressly provided for under this License.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.termination.p0.s2">Any attempt otherwise to
do so is void.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.termination.p0.s3">If you violate this License, any copyright holder may
put you on notice by notifying you of the violation, by any reasonable
means, provided 60 days have not elapsed since the last violation.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.termination.p0.s4">Having put you on notice, the copyright holder may then terminate your
license at any time.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.termination.p0.s5">However, parties who have received copies, or
rights, from you under this License will not have their licenses
terminated so long as they remain in full compliance.</sent>
</p>

</section>
<section id="gfdl.futurevisions" name="10. FUTURE REVISIONS OF THIS LICENSE">
<title>10. FUTURE REVISIONS OF THIS LICENSE</title>
<p id="gfdl.futurevisions.p0">
 <sent id="gfdl.futurevisions.p0.s1">The Free Software Foundation may publish new, revised versions
of the GNU Free Documentation License from time to time.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.futurevisions.p0.s2">Such new
versions will be similar in spirit to the present version, but may
differ in detail to address new problems or concerns.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.futurevisions.p0.s3">See
http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.futurevisions.p1">
 <sent id="gfdl.futurevisions.p1.s1">Each version of the License is given a distinguishing version number.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.futurevisions.p1.s2">If the Work specifies that a particular numbered version of this
License "or any later version" applies to it, you have the option of
following the terms and conditions either of that specified version or
of any later version that has been published (not as a draft) by the
Free Software Foundation.</sent>
 <sent id="gfdl.futurevisions.p1.s3">If the Work does not specify a version
number of this License, you may choose any version ever published (not
as a draft) by the Free Software Foundation.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gfdl.futurevisions.p2">
 <sent id="gfdl.futurevisions.p2.s1">For instructions on how to use this License,
see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/.</sent>
</p>
</section>
  </body>
</gpl>


