<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="selectxpath.xsl" type="text/xsl" ?>
<!DOCTYPE gpl SYSTEM "http://gplv3.fsf.org/comments/gpl3.dtd">
<!-- $Id$ -->
<gpl>
  <head>
    <title>GNU Simpler Free Documentation License</title>
    <pubdate>Discussion Draft 1 of Version 1, September 2006</pubdate>
<status>THIS IS A DRAFT, NOT A PUBLISHED VERSION OF THE GNU SIMPLER FREE DOCUMENTATION LICENSE.</status> 
    <copyright>
      <year>2000, 2002, 2006</year>
      <holder>Free Software Foundation, Inc.</holder>
    </copyright>
    <legalnotice>
      <address>
        <name>Free Software Foundation, Inc.</name>
        <street>51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor</street>,
        <city>Boston</city>,
        <state>MA</state>
        <postcode>02110-1301</postcode>
        <country>USA</country>
      </address>
      <p>Everyone is permitted to copy and distribute verbatim copies of this license document, but changing it is not allowed.</p>
    </legalnotice>
    <releaseinfo>Fri 22 September 2006</releaseinfo>
    </head>

  <body>
    <title>GNU Simpler Free Documentation License</title>

    <section id="gsfdl.preamble" name="What This License Does">
      <title>WHAT THIS LICENSE DOES</title>

<p id="gsfdl.preamble.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p0.s1">The purpose of this License is to make a work of authorship free.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p0.s2">This means giving all users the four essential freedoms:</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.preamble.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p1.s1">0. The freedom to read, view, or use the work.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p1.s2">1. The freedom to change the work, with access to formats which make that convenient to do.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p1.s3">2. The freedom to make and redistribute copies of the work.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p1.s4">3. The freedom to distribute modified versions.<br/></sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.preamble.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p2.s1">Secondarily, this License assures the author and publisher the credit for their work, while sparing any appearance of being responsible for modifications made by others.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.preamble.p3">
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p3.s1">This License is a kind of "copyleft", which means that derivative works of the document must themselves be free in the same sense.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p3.s2">It complements the GNU General Public License, which is a copyleft license designed for free software.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.preamble.p4">
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p4.s1">This License is not limited to "documentation", or even to works that
are textual; it can be used for any work of authorship meant for human
appreciation, rather than machine execution.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p4.s2">We recommend this
License principally for works whose purpose is instruction or
reference, but it can be used for any work regardless of the subject
matter, even for art and fiction.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.preamble.p4.s3">The only kind of work for which
this should not be used is software.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.freemanuals" name="0a. Free Manuals Are Essential">
<title>0a. FREE MANUALS ARE ESSENTIAL</title>
<p id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p0.s1">Free manuals are essential for free software.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p0.s2">Users must have freedom
to redistribute (including commercial sale of printed copies), so that
the manual, on-line or on paper, can accompany every copy of the
program.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p0.s3">When users modify the program, adding or changing features,
they must be free to update the manual too, to keep it accurate.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p1.s1">Although free manuals are essential, many important free programs lack
good free reference manuals and free introductory texts.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p1.s2">Sometimes
this is because the programs' developers wrote non-free manuals, not
recognizing the need for documentation to be free.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p1.s3">Please help spread
the the word that free software needs free reference manuals and free
tutorials.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p2.s1">You can encourage commercial publishers to publish more free manuals
and textbooks by buying printed copies of them, and by rejecting
non-free manuals.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p2.s2">Pay money for value, but don't pay with your freedom.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p3">
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p3.s1">If you are writing a manual or textbook, please insist on publishing
it under a free license.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p3.s2">Don't let a publisher talk you out of it; if
one publisher refuses to use a free license, switch to one that will.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.freemanuals.p3.s3">If you're not sure whether a proposed license is free, write to
&lt;licensing@gnu.org&gt;.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.applicdef" name="1. Applicability and Definitions">
<title>1. APPLICABILITY AND DEFINITIONS</title>

<p id="gsfdl.applicdef.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p0.s1">In this License, each licensee is addressed as "you," while "the
Work" refers to any work, in any medium, that contains a notice placed
by the copyright holder saying it can be distributed under the terms
of this License.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p0.s2">It may physically consist of multiple volumes.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p0.s3">A
"modified" work includes versions that have been translated,
transformed, or adapted, or to which material has been added.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p0.s4">A work
"based on" another work means any modified version for which
permission is necessary under applicable copyright law.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.applicdef.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p1.s1">To "propagate" a work means doing anything with it that requires
permission under applicable copyright law, except making modifications
that you do not share.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p1.s2">Propagation includes copying, distribution
(with or without modification), making available or communicating to
the public,publicly displaying or performing the work and in some
countries other activities as well.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p1.s3">To "convey" a work means any kind
of propagation that enables other parties to make or receive copies,
excluding sublicensing.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.applicdef.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p2.s1">A "Transparent" copy of the Work means a machine-readable copy,
represented in a format whose specification is available to the
general public, that is suitable for revision straightforwardly by
generic editors appropriate to the medium (text, sound, video, etc.),
and that is suitable (perhaps through programmed format conversion) for
input to a wide variety of programs for processing that medium.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p2.s2">Material stored in an otherwise Transparent file format in a way that
thwarts or discourages subsequent substantial modification by others
is not Transparent.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p2.s3">A copy that is not "Transparent" is called
"Opaque".</sent>
</p>


<p id="gsfdl.applicdef.p3">
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p3.s1">Examples of suitable formats for Transparent copies of textual works
include plain ASCII without markup, Texinfo input format, LaTeX input
format, SGML or XML using a publicly available DTD or schema,
OpenDocument format, and standard-conforming simple HTML, PostScript
or PDF designed for human modification.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p3.s2">Examples of transparent image
formats include PNG, XCF and JPG.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p3.s3">Examples of transparent video
formats include MPEG2 and Ogg Theora.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p3.s4">Opaque formats include
proprietary formats that can be read and edited only by proprietary
word processors, SGML or XML for which the DTD, schema and/or
processing tools are not generally available, and the
machine-generated HTML, PostScript or PDF produced by some word
processors for output purposes only.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.applicdef.p4">
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p4.s1">The "Title Page" means the portion of the work where information such
as title, authors, date of publication, and copyright notice would
normally appear.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.applicdef.p5">
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p5.s1">A section "Entitled XYZ" means a named section of the Work whose
title either is precisely XYZ or contains XYZ in parentheses following
text that translates XYZ in another language.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p5.s2">(Here XYZ stands for a
specific section name mentioned below, such as "Acknowledgements",
"Dedications", "Endorsements", or "History".)</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p5.s3">To "Preserve the Title"
of such a section when you modify the Work means that it remains a
section "Entitled XYZ" according to this definition.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.applicdef.p6">
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p6.s1">The Work may include Warranty Disclaimers next to the notice which
states that this License applies to the Work.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.applicdef.p6.s2">These Warranty
Disclaimers are considered to be included by reference in this
License, but only as regards disclaiming warranties: any other
implication that these Warranty Disclaimers may have is void and has
no effect on the meaning of this License.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.basicperms" name="1a. Basic Permissions">
<title>1a. BASIC PERMISSIONS</title>

<p id="gsfdl.basicperms.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.basicperms.p0.s1">You have a world-wide, royalty-free license, for the duration of the
copyright on the Work, to use the Work under the conditions stated
herein.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.basicperms.p0.s2">You accept the license if you propagate the Work.</sent>
</p>

</section>


<section id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying" name="2. Verbatim Copying">
<title>2. VERBATIM COPYING</title>

<p id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p0.s1">You may propagate the Work unmodified in any medium, either
commercially or noncommercially, provided that this License, the
copyright notices, and the license notice saying this License applies
to the Work are reproduced in all copies, and that you add no
other conditions whatsoever to those of this License.</sent>
</p>

<p id="verbatimcopying.p1">
 <sent id="verbatimcopying.p1.s1">You need not include a copy of this License in the Work if you have
registered the work's license with a national agency that maintains a
network server through which the general public can find out its
license.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p2.s1">You may not apply technical measures to obstruct or control the use or
further copying of any copies you make or distribute, by those to whom
they may be distributed.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p2.s2">However, you may charge a fee in exchange
for copies.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p3.s3">You may transmit copies with methods that give you legal
rights to control further use, copying or transmission, only on
condition that you waive the use of those legal rights to impose any
conditions aside from those of this License.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p4.s1">You may also lend copies, under the same conditions stated above, and
you may publicly display copies.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.verbatimcopying.p4.s2">You may publically perform the
Work provided you make a transparent copy of the document
available as described in section 3 as though you had distributed
opaque copies to the audience.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.copyinquantity" name="3. Copying in Quantity">
<title>3. COPYING IN QUANTITY</title>

<p id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p0.s1">If you publish printed copies (or copies in media that commonly have
printed covers) of the Work, numbering more than 100, the front
cover must clearly and unambiguously present the full title.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p0.s2">Copying
with changes limited to the covers, under these conditions, can be
treated as verbatim copying in other respects.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p1.s1">If you convey Opaque copies of the Work numbering
more than 100, you must also convey a corresponding
machine-readable Transparent version.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p1.s2">The Transparent version need
not have identical formatting as long as its contents are the same and
are clearly visible, and non-textual contents have equal or superior
resolution and quality.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p1.s3">When you convey the Opaque copies by
offering access to copy from a designated place, you must offer
equivalent access to copy the Transparent version from the same place.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p1.s4">Otherwise, you must convey a machine-readable Transparent copy
along with each Opaque copy, or state in or with each Opaque copy a
computer-network location from which the general network-using public
has anonymous gratis access to download, using public-standard network
protocols, a corresponding Transparent copy of the Work.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p1.s5">Under
the latter option, you must take reasonably prudent steps, when you
begin conveying of Opaque copies in quantity, to ensure that this
Transparent copy will remain thus accessible at the stated location
until at least one year after the last time you convey an Opaque
copy (directly or through your agents or retailers) of that edition to
the public.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.copyinquantity.p2.s1">It is requested, but not required, that you contact the authors of the
Work well before conveying any large number of copies, to give
them a chance to provide you with an updated version of the Work.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.modifications" name="4. Modifications">
<title>4. MODIFICATIONS</title>

<p id="gsfdl.modifications.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p0.s1">You may convey a Modified Version of the Work under
the conditions of sections 2 and 3 above, provided that you release
the Modified Version under precisely this License, with the Modified
Version filling the role of the Work, thus licensing distribution
and modification of the Modified Version to whoever possesses a copy
of it.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p0.s2">In addition, you must do these things in the Modified Version:</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.modifications.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s1">A. Use a title distinct
   from that of the Work, and from those of previous versions
   of the Work as listed in the History section.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s2">B. List as authors (on the Title Page, if any), one or more persons or entities
   responsible for authorship of the modifications in the Modified Version.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s3">C. Credit (on the Title Page, if any) at least five of the principal authors of
   the Work (all of them, if it has fewer than five) if the material
   derived from the Work is more than 1/4 of the total.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s4">D. Prominently state the name of the publisher of the Modified Version.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s5">E. Preserve all the copyright notices of the Work.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s6">F. Add an appropriate copyright notice for your modifications
   adjacent to the other copyright notices.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s7">G. Include, immediately after the copyright notices, a license notice
   giving the public permission to use the Modified Version under the
   terms of this License, in the form shown in the Addendum below.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s8">H. Include an unaltered copy of this License.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s9">I. Preserve the section Entitled "History", Preserve its Title, and add
   to it an item stating at least the title, year, new authors, and
   publisher of the Modified Version.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s10">If
   there is no section Entitled "History" in the Work, create one
   stating the title, year, authors, and publisher of the Work,
   then add an item describing the Modified
   Version as stated in the previous sentence.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s11">J. Preserve the network location, if any, given in the Work for
   public access to a Transparent copy of the Work, and likewise
   the network locations given in the Work for previous versions
   it was based on.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s12">These may be placed in the "History" section.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s13">You may omit a network location for a work that was published at
   least four years before the Work itself.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s14">K. For any section Entitled "Acknowledgements" or "Dedications",
   Preserve the Title of the section, and preserve in the section all
   the substance and tone of each of the contributor acknowledgements
   and/or dedications given therein.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s15">Acknowledgments and Dedications
   can be deleted when a Modified Version deletes all material to
   which the Acknowledgments and Dedications could reasonably have 
   applied.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s16">L. Delete any section Entitled "Endorsements".<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s17">Such a section
   may not be included in the Modified Version.<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s18">M. Do not retitle any existing section to be Entitled "Endorsements".<br/></sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p1.s19">N. Preserve any Warranty Disclaimers.<br/></sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.modifications.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p2.s1">Authors and publishers of previous versions can release you from above
requirements to cite or refer to them or their versions.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.modifications.p3">
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p3.s1">You may add a section Entitled "Endorsements", provided it contains
nothing but endorsements of your Modified Version by various
parties--for example, statements of peer review or that the text has
been approved by an organization as the authoritative definition of a
standard.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.modifications.p4">
 <sent id="gsfdl.modifications.p4.s1">The author(s) and publisher(s) of the Work do not by this License
give permission to use their names for publicity for or to assert or
imply endorsement of any Modified Version.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.combinations" name="5. Combinations">
<title>5. COMBINATIONS</title>

<p id="gsfdl.combinations.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.combinations.p0.s1">You may combine the Work with other works released under this
License, under the terms defined in section 4 above for modified
versions.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.combinations.p0.s2">Clause 4C applies to all the principal authors of all the
combined documents, taken together.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.combinations.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.combinations.p1.s1">The combined work need only contain one copy of this License.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.combinations.p1.s2">In the
combination, you must preserve all warranty disclaimers, combine any
sections Entitled "History" in the various original works, forming
one section Entitled "History"; likewise combine any sections Entitled
"Acknowledgements", and any sections Entitled "Dedications".</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.combinations.p1.s3">You must
delete all sections Entitled "Endorsements".</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.collections" name="6. Collections of Documents">
<title>6. COLLECTIONS</title>

<p id="gsfdl.collections.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.collections.p0.s1">You may make a collection consisting of the Work and other works
released under this License, and replace the individual copies of this
License in the various works with a single copy that is included in
the collection, provided that you follow the rules of this License for
verbatim copying of each of the works in all other respects.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.collections.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.collections.p1.s1">You may extract one of the collected works from such a collection, and distribute
it individually under this License, provided you insert a copy of this
License into the extracted work, and follow this License in all
other respects regarding verbatim copying of that work.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.excerpts" name="6a. Excerpts">
<title>6a. EXCERPTS</title>

<p id="gsfdl.excerpts.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.excerpts.p0.s1">You may publish a work, a Modified Version, or a collection, of up
to 20,000 characters of text (excluding formatting mark-up) in
electronic form, or up to 12 normal printed pages, or up to a minute
of audio or video, as an Excerpt.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.excerpts.p0.s2">An Excerpt follows the applicable
rules of this license, except that the following required
materials--the copy of this license, title page materials, historical
copyright notices, warranty disclaimers, and any required
sections--may be replaced by one or more publicly accessible URLs
referring to the same materials.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.aggregation" name="7. Aggregation with Independent Works">
<title>7. AGGREGATION WITH INDEPENDENT WORKS</title>

<p id="gsfdl.aggregation.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.aggregation.p0.s1">A compilation of the Work or its derivatives with other separate
and independent works, in or on a volume of a storage or
distribution medium, is called an "aggregate" if the combination and the copyright
resulting from the compilation are not used to limit the legal rights
of the compilation's users beyond what the individual works permit.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.aggregation.p0.s2">Including the Work in an aggregate does not cause this License to
apply to the other works in the aggregate which are not themselves
derivative works of the Work.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.translation" name="8. Translation">
<title>8. TRANSLATION</title>

<p id="gsfdl.translation.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.translation.p0.s1">Translation is considered a kind of modification, so you may
distribute translations of the Work under the terms of section 4.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.translation.p0.s2">You may include a translation of this License, and all the license
notices in the Work, and any Warrany Disclaimers, provided that
you also include the original English version of this License and the
original versions of those notices and disclaimers.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.translation.p0.s3">In case of a
disagreement between the translation and the original version of this
License or a notice or disclaimer, the original version will prevail.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.translation.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.translation.p1.s1">If a section in the Work is Entitled "Acknowledgements",
"Dedications", or "History", the requirement (section 4) to Preserve
its Title (section 1) will typically require changing the actual
title.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.termination" name="9. Termination">
<title>9. TERMINATION</title>

<p id="gsfdl.termination.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.termination.p0.s1">You may not propagate or modify the Work except as
expressly provided for under this License.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.termination.p0.s2">Any attempt otherwise to
do so is void.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.termination.p0.s3">If you violate this License, any copyright holder may
put you on notice by notifying you of the violation, by any reasonable
means, provided 60 days have not elapsed since the last violation.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.termination.p0.s4">Having put you on notice, the copyright holder may then terminate your
license at any time.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.termination.p0.s5">However, parties who have received copies, or
rights, from you under this License will not have their licenses
terminated so long as they remain in full compliance.</sent>
</p>
</section>

<section id="gsfdl.futurevisions" name="10. Future Revisions of this License">
<title>10. FUTURE REVISIONS OF THIS LICENSE</title>

<p id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p0">
 <sent id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p0.s1">The Free Software Foundation may publish new, revised versions of the
GNU Simpler Free Documentation License from time to time.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p0.s2">Such new
versions will be similar in spirit to the present version, but may
differ in detail to address new problems or concerns.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p0.s3">See
http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p1">
 <sent id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p1.s1">Each version of the License is given a distinguishing version number.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p1.s2">If the Work specifies that a particular numbered version of this
License "or any later version" applies to it, you have the option of
following the terms and conditions either of that specified version or
of any later version that has been published (not as a draft) by the
Free Software Foundation.</sent>
 <sent id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p1.s3">If the Work does not specify a version
number of this License, you may choose any version ever published (not
as a draft) by the Free Software Foundation.</sent>
</p>

<p id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p2">
 <sent id="gsfdl.futurevisions.p2.s1">For instructions on how to use this License,
see http://www.gnu.org/licenses/.</sent>
</p>

</section>
  </body>
</gpl>
